Stephen Trudell

steviejtrudell@gmail.com
Austin, TX 78749
(737) 402-0876

About

Full stack web developer leveraging experience in audio engineering to deliver creative solutions in a wide range of project types. I recently earned my certificate from the Code Bootcamp at UT Austin, specializing in MERN stack. With excellent time management, work ethic, attention to detail, and customer service skills learned in the unpredictable environments of the music and food service industries, I am both flexible and quick to adapt to new and changing work settings. I am well known as reliable, friendly, and easy to work with in both large and small scale teams, and am highly responsible and productive when working independently. I am excited to enter the diverse field of web development and offer my unique perspective and problem solving experience.

Skills

Certification 9

Full Stack Web Development

The University of Texas at Austin - 2022

<u>Client Side</u>	<u>Technologies</u>
JavaScript	PWAs
React	SPAs
CSS	Swipe
HTML	Jest
Bootstrap	Git
Mobile Responsive	Heroku
Server Side	<u>DevOps</u>
Server Side Node	<u>DevOps</u> MERN Stack
Node	MERN Stack
Node Express	MERN Stack AGILE
Node Express GraphQL	MERN Stack AGILE MVC

Experience

2010 - Present

Audio Engineer / Musician Various - Austin, TX

- Recording, mixing, and mastering audio using Pro Tools, Ableton Live, Print Music, SSL Native and Waves plugins.
- Working in chaotic and radid fire production/performance settings, both in the studio and on stage.
- Intuition in finding creative solutions to unrehearsed problems.
- Collaborating with a wide spectrum of colorful humans as composers, band mates, crew mates, clients, and audiences.

2013 - Present

Cashier / Food Prep / Driver The Soup Peddler - Austin, TX

- Self-sufficiency and a strong work ethic developed in a small workforce within a small company.
- Administering customer service skills and time management techniques in a restaurant environment.

2006 - 2013

Cashier

H-E-B Groceries - Bee Cave, TX

 Customer service and team work skills developed in a large workforce within a large company.

Education

A.A. In Foreign Language: French Austin Community College - 2013

References

Available upon request.

PORTFOLIO

https://strudelandcoffee.github.io/react-portfolio

n 🕨

https://www.linkedin.com/in/stevie-trudell-atx

https://github.com/strudelAndCoffee